Hello, welcome to another exciting video. My name is Kimo Jello and in these tutorial series
in this series we're going to be building south applications. I'm going to show you step
by step on how to build south applications from scratch to production and it's going
to be a very very interesting series. So the goal of this video it's going to be a very
very interesting series. The goal of this series is to learn how to build south applications
and I want to tell you out of biotagon. Now this is not a quick get-reward scheme because
you know whatever it is that you want to do is going to take so much time it's going
to require so much dedication and this also if it is something that you really want to
do if south application building south application is something that you really want to do
then it's going to take so much time it's going to take more than just one south applications,
one south application to get to get money but it's you're going to get there with a lot of
dedications and we're going to do this from all right the first thing when it comes to building
a south application is to identify a problem you know what problem are you trying to solve now
for the most part you know you need to you need to sit down and ask ourselves is this a problem
that we have to solve we is this a problem that really needs solving and can it be solved using
a software that's the first thing that we need to do and in this case what we are trying to solve
basically is to you know allow content creators to upload audio or video and try and transcribe it
and help them transcribe those videos and also generate chapters and also auto-report
with these videos into different social media platforms so that's the south applications that
we are building and that leads to the next part of this which is what are your target audience now
for the most part for us our target audience in this first south application is content creators
people who create content and podcasts who just want to transcribe their audience or videos
and also generate different chapters and optimize their final product the next part of this is
duration or how long is this south application going to take now the goal of this one is just to
take two to three weeks to build because you know we are busy developers so we're going to try as
much as possible to build something that we can finish within a timeframe of which in time
three weeks timeframe so that's what we are going to be building how the next part is the
tech stack tech stack is very very important when it comes to if your solo developer tech stack is
one of the most important it's very very important because like knowing what tech stack to use is
going to allow you is going to speed up your development process and you know in this case we are
going to be using throughout this series we're going to be using fast API and next year's the reason
why you ideally are used roast axon for most of the things that I do but one of the reasons why I
switch to fast api is because it's easy and it's fast to build stuff so we're going to be
using fast API to build all the APIs our backend services and in the front end we're going to be
using next years to build the front end and the user interfaces all right and another thing also
we're going to be using charge gpt i'm going to show you exactly how to use charge gpt as a
supplement code editor to speed up the process and also throughout this series i'm going to show
you the best practices how to build your own templates boilerplate templates that speed up your
process so that you know in the next sas project that we are going to be building together we
don't have to do all of these things that we are going to be doing in the first sas template so
the first project is going to be very very slow it's going to be quite a long one but
I'm at promise it's going to worth it so watch through all these